
export const data = [
    {
      question: "What year was master frosty created?",
      option1: "Year 2020",
      option2: "Year 2022",
      option3: "Year 2024",
      option4: "Year 2023",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Mention two MasterFrosty brand colors",
      option1: "Purple, Pink",
      option2: "pink, Brown ",
      option3: "Purple, Black",
      option4: "Purple, Lailac",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the founder of MasterFrosty",
      option1: "Daramola Tokunbo",
      option2: "Daramola Femi",
      option3: "David Victor",
      option4: "Habeeb Juwon",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of this URL is the correct web url of MasterFrosty",
      option1: "https://www.frosty.com",
      option2: "https://www.masterfrostyy.com",
      option3: "https://www.masterrfrosty.com",
      option4: "https://www.masterfrosty.com",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "The most popular product in master frosty is?",
      option1: "Turkey-mid-wings",
      option2: "Susage",
      option3: "Salmon fish",
      option4: "Croaker",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Where is MasterFrosty Located?",
      option1: "Along Ede Rd OPP Bovas filling Sation",
      option2: "Along Ondo Rd OPP poplat",
      option3: "Beside Energy along, Ibadan Rd Ile-ife",
      option4: "Mayfair Market Central",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What's the motor of the brand?",
      option1: "Delight frozen foods within your comfort zone",
      option2: "Frozen delight within your comfort zone",
      option3: "Tasty frozen foods",
      option4: "Best frozen foods",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the correct instagram handle of MasterFrosty?",
      option1: "master_frosty1",
      option2: "master.frosty1",
      option3: "masterfrosty_1",
      option4: "masterfrosty01",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these categories of produce is MasterFrosty specialize in",
      option1: "soft drinks, seaFoods, snacks",
      option2: "Kunu, zobo, Goat meat",
      option3: "Dryfish, Frozen meat",
      option4: "Frozen foods, sea foods, frozen meat",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What's MasterFrosty known for?",
      option1: "Fancy interior",
      option2: "Cheap Goods",
      option3: "Good customer service and swift delivery",
      option4: "i dont know ðŸ™„",
      ans: 3,
    },
  ];